

DANIEL BATANOV

Experienced professional passionate about building engaging, user-friendly applications. About two years ago, I found a new passion for coding. During that time I worked my skills up through various courses, projects, and internships. My previous experience in Architecture and QA testing has instilled a strong work ethic and a proactive mindset.

Satanoff.s@protonmail.com Satanoff.sgt.spt.satanoff.sgt.spt.satanoff.sgt.sqt.satanoff.sgt.sqt.satanoff.sgt.sqt.satanoff.sgt.sqt.satanoff.sqt.sqt.satanoff.sqt.sqt.satanoff.sqt.sqt.sqt.satanoff.sqt.sqt.satanoff.sqt.sqt.satanoff.sqt.sqt.satanoff.sqt.sqt.satanoff.sqt.sqt.satanoff.sqt.sqt.satanoff.sqt.sqt.satanoff.sqt.sqt.satanoff.sqt.sqt.sqt.satanoff.sqt.sqt.satanoff.sqt.sqt.satanoff.sqt.sqt.satanoff.sqt.sqt.satanoff.sqt.sqt.satanoff.sqt.sqt.sqt.satanoff.sqt.sqt.satanoff.sqt.sqt.satanoff.sqt.sqt.satanoff.sqt.sqt.satanoff.sqt.sqt.satanoff.sqt.sqt.satanoff.sqt.sqt.satanoff.sqt.sqt.satanoff.sqt.sqt.satanoff.sqt.sqt.satanoff.sqt.sqt.satanoff

PROJECTS

Ra-auth-ui (open source) (library) Github | npm

Out of the box authentication lavouts, hooks and pipelines to integrate into react-admin framework

Book Store (full-stack) (Stripe) Live | Github | Video

An e-commerce website for books with an admin panel, Stipe payments and more

Mini Finance (Softuniada 2024) Live | Github

A finance web app, offering virtual cards, top-ups, friend connections, transactions and history tracking

Ai Builder (full-stack) (OpenAI) Github

A webpage builder that leverages the OpenAI API to generate and display webpages based on user prompts

Crops Info (full-stack)

A comprehensive wiki for crops, providing users with information like cultivation, pests, dieses, nutrition etc.

SKILLS

Tech skills

JavaScript ES6+ | HTML5 | CSS | SASS | Tailwind

React | Typescript | Angular

NodeJS | Express | Handlebars

Chai | Mocha | Playwright | Jest

MongoDB | Mongoose | MySQL

Git | NPM | Yarn | HTTP | REST | AJAX

Soft skills

Problem-solving (Growth mindset (Motivation)

Communication (Teamwork) Time management

CERTIFICATES / ACHIEVEMENTS

- Front-End Developer SoftUni
- Softuniada Programming Olympiad Top 10

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

SoftUni | Web development **UAECG** | Master of Architecture High School of Mathematics | IT

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Full-stack Developer Intern

Cost-Effective Solutions

Dec 2024 - Now

- Focus on backend with Node, postgreSQL, Prisma
- Building a scraper software for NGO organization
- · Working in a team of 8 individuals
- · Following best practices for clean code

Front-end Developer Intern

Humble Software Ltd

March - Dec 2024

- · Working closely with a senior tech lead
- Building internal libraries based on React Admin

Architect

IPA architecture and more 2021 - 2023

Intern Architect

Design Art "K&K" 2018 - 2019

Intern Architect

Integra Consult Project 2017 - 2018

Manual OA

Gameloft 2014 - 2015

- Developed over 100 unique test cases
- Assisted other teams during overtime to resolve major issues

LANGUAGES

English Proficient



Bulgarian Native

